One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
I'm too excited to wait for morning to come. (I can't wait)
And so we might as well just grab the sun,
And forcefully drag it into the sky! Go!
That's right, we're Shining! Running! Forever!
Weave the fragments of our dreams together!
When they become one, that will be our treasure!
Let's go Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Law's New Strategy and
the Colosseum's Underground Nightmare!
You're Black Leg from the Straw Hats, right?
Diable Jambe!
Premier Hachis!
Penta-Chromatic String!
Sanji-san!
Let's see if you can protect your crew!
He's coming for us!
You've gotta be kidding!
Diable Jambe!
Poêle à Frire...
Frying Pan...
Spectre!
You're pretty tough.
W-What's this?!
I can't move!
What? Sanji-san's frozen mid-air!
He cannot move.
The young master's power has stopped him.
Black Leg is like a fly trapped in a spider's web.
He can only await his death!
What is that?!
A whip?!
Stay out of this! Run!
Get out of here with a Coup de Burst!
We can't leave you!
Overheat!
Sanji!
Sanji-kun, get out of there!
Shambles!
Room!
Law?
Dressrosa
Run!
It's Traf! He saved Sanji!
Sorry, this is my fault.
I'll take us to the ship.
Traf-san?
Sanji!
Dammit, I'm back on this ship!
Caesar!
Oh, Jora! Help me!
I am a prisoner as well.
I got careless.
Doflamingo's attacking again!
Black Legger.
How are you guys doing with the destruction of the factory?
Franky said he knows where it is, but that destroying it will be difficult.
Where is Father?! And Kanjurou?!
San-goro!
The samurai's inside the factory too.
We will be able to save him.
We still need more time, huh?
Hey you! Is that my heart?!
Were you keeping it in the cabin?!
This one is mine. I had your heart.
What?!
Damn it!
S-So you were storing it inside your own chest?!
You guys.
You have to go to Zou with this guy, right now.
Zou?
Didn't I give you a Vivre Card pointing toward the next island?
We're moving on? But what about Luffy-san and the others?!
Once the factory is destroyed, we're done here.
We'll catch up with you soon enough.
No, we have to wait!
We can't set sail without our captain!
We are the Straw Hat Pirates!
A warship's flying straight toward us!
Why?!
Fujitora, huh?
And Doflamingo's coming from the other direction!
You can stay if you want to, but don't let them have Caesar.
Fire!
Something's falling from the sky!
Meteors?!
Room!
Traf-kun! The "Swirly Hat Pirates" are setting sail!
Get going!
Hey, Law!
I understand that we have to get Caesar away from here...
and I'm fine with moving forward...
but...
Dressrosa was supposed to be a brief stop.
Our ultimate goal was to take down the Emperor Kaidou, right?
Don't you think... you're focusing too much on Doflamingo?
Meteors! Meteors!
Tact!
Isshou-san, there's a hole in the hull!
Oh, what a blunder. So Law-san was down there.
Is this really the time to be eating?!
Let's just go back to Dressrosa.
The tide of war...
will shift soon, it seems.
Give the order to turn around!
You're not getting away!
It's that whip again!
Joker, help me!
Overheat!
Namier! Listen up.
You have to find a path without clouds!
Doflamingo ate the String Fruit.
He can attach threads to clouds and move through the air.
He can't follow you if the sky is clear!
Threads? I see.
Just go already!
Here goes! Coup de Burst!
Look, Doflamingo!
Law, what are you doing?!
Young master, don't worry about me!
What are you hoping to achieve by letting half of the Straw Hats escape?
The rest of them are still on Dressrosa.
I just have to take them all hostage, and I'll have Caesar back in no time.
Didn't you say that underestimating them was a fatal mistake?
It's a shame, but my alliance with the Straw Hats ends here.
I teamed up with them for one goal.
I was merely using them to stop the Smile production.
Even if I can't take you down personally,
if you lose the Smiles,
you'll soon be killed by Kaidou.
I see.
So you hoped to take me down with you.
I'd like to see the chaos your death will bring to the world,
but my main priority is settling the score for what happened thirteen years ago,
Joker!
What are you planning to do to Jora?
You should know what kind of family we are.
That's right, Law!
If it's for the young master then I'm always ready to sacrifice my-
You should run as far as possible.
Yes!
Seeing as Black Leg just showed up before,
clearly things haven't gone as I planned.
Your grudge against me is completely unjustified, Law!
This isn't a grudge.
Accomplishing that person's greatest desire,
is the only reason I've lived for until today!
Off Dressrosa's Coast
Is Traf gonna be okay?
Hey, are you guys keeping a proper lookout?
This is Brook, I see no problems from my 45° angle.
If he comes anywhere near us,
I'll just use this to create a gust of wind and blow away the clouds.
Then he won't be able to follow us anymore.
In any case, you guys have to protect Robin-chan with your lives!
Got it!
How are they?
My precious Robin-chan is with Franky and Usopp.
Now we just have to hope that Zoro can meet up with Luffy.
Yeah, Law's plan is to leave Doflamingo alive and have him fight the Emperor Kaidou.
So long as he runs away, he won't die.
What's wrong, Momo?
Why are you in your dragon form?
I-I can't stop shaking.
That flying man...
When we were here before, I saw him once.
Young master, he'll die!
Just what the hell was that?!
What are you?!
Aren't you a gladiator?!
Who'd enjoy watching you just run around?
If you can't cut up your opponents,
then let yourself get cut and show them some blood.
All humans, no matter their personality,
have a cruel side that lusts for blood.
Blood and death.
That is the ultimate entertainment!
Get a hold of yourself!
Damn trash...
Never let me see a pathetic match like today again.
Y-Yes, young master!
Kin'emon, Momonosuke...
Oh, it's you, Kanjurou.
I found the port.
Let's get a ship from there.
This is a dangerous country.
When I think of Kanjurou as his prisoner, I get this uneasy feeling.
Please be safe, Kanjurou...
What sort of ridiculous expression is that?!
This all depends on what he wants you for, but...
they might not treat their hostages all that badly.
So it's okay.
You don't care at all!
You're thinking of something else, aren't you?!
Speaking of that, Violet-chan said she'd be fine too.
I'll be fine.
I asked an acquaintance of mine, so I'll be protected by the government.
They should already be waiting for me at the port.
I see.
I wish I could go with you, but at least I know you'll be safe.
Thank you.
Thanks to you, I'm finally able to move forward again.
It was nothing.
If you want to thank me, then a kiss on my che-
Oh no, your ship is being attacked by Fighting Fish!
Fighting Fish?
What's that?!
Hurry, you must go to them.
Nami-swan!
Kill her!
Damn that Rebecca!
As usual, she just won't die!
Hurry up and die, you little brat!
Horse-san!
Yes?
Please take me to the palace.
Yes ma'am!
Dressrosa
Corrida Colosseum
Why are you crying?
Why do you know who Luffy and I are?
I'be albayz bween your ban!
I've always been your fan!
We're not getting anywhere with this guy.
C-C-Could I have your auto-
C-Can I have your autograph!?
There, I said it.
Autograph?
I'll go look for Luffy-senpai, so please give me your autograph!
You'll look for him?
Thanks.
Hurry up!
Th-
Th?
Then...
Just wait for a bit.
Even if it costs me my life, I'll find him!
You're gonna risk your life?
You damn...
Damn it!
She just won't go down!
This is Rebecca's specialty, the Backwater Sword Dance!
Become strong, Rebecca!
Using her opponents momentum, she brings them close to the edge of the ring.
With her back to the Fighting-Fish infested water,
and her amazing speed, she uses her opponent's strength to push them in the water!
This is it!
This is the Backwater Sword Dance!
Yes, in all her previous matches,
she has never directly harmed a single person!
Prisoner Gladiator Lodging
So she can use Observation Haki?
Haki?
She's never taken an attack from anyone either!
She's dropped every opponent out of the ring!
She's the undefeated woman!
She's really good!
Keep it up, Rebecca!
Her fighting style is not unbeautiful,
and to be honest, I don't dislike it!
But how will she go with this competition!?
With powerhouses gathered from all over the world and their varied fighting styles,
there's no guarantee that they'll play fair!
Southern Majiatsuka Kingdom
Military Commander
Rolling Logan
Let's see, should I break your bones, hated one?
Next!
Is Contestant Sai from the Flower Country here?
Inside the Colosseum
Underground Medical Treatment Facility Waiting Room
Why are you calling "Next"?!
You just carried our Grandpa in there,
and he hasn't come out yet!
Oh, you mean Contestant Chinjao?
Did Grandpa die?
Huh? What's going on?
Shut it, you damn martial artist!
Our Grandpa is practically indestructible, but he's getting pretty old.
If he's lying dead in there,
then just tell me that he's dead!
He's so noisy.
You're being too dramatic.
He has already left the treatment area.
There is an exit at the back of the hospital room...
so after he was treated,
he wouldn't come back this way.
Oh, I see. Sorry for the disturbance.
Now you understand? Well then, come on in.
I'm so sorry I misunderstood. I was wrong.
How can I ever make up for this?
See, I'm on my knees! Please forgive me!
Don't mind him.
His feelings tend to get the better of him.
I... I see.
Contestant Sai from the Flower Country, yes?
That's right.
Let us begin the operation.
What?!
Next.
What's this? A toy?
A mountain of toys?
Toys and warriors.
Who's there?!
You're... Hajrudin?!
Why're... all of you here?
Gramps! You're alright!
That's a relief.
I see nothing to be relieved about, you clown!
It seems like all the losers of this tournament
are thrown down here.
What?!
What is the meaning of this?! Where's the exit?
You really think there'd be one?!
That bastard Doflamingo tricked us.
This means war, Elizabello-sama.
Indeed. But I can't believe that
my King Punch is ineffective against this wall.
We're underground, you know.
In other words, these walls are the earth itself.
No matter how strong your punches might be,
you can't break through these walls.
What is he hoping to accomplish by trapping us here?
I seriously doubt they'll treat our wounds down here.
Unless Doflamingo has a really good explanation...
I will curse him down to his grandchildren's generation!
Translation & initial timing, Tsuki, Yibis (Opening)
Timing, Galaxy 9000, , Time-checking, Sewil
Quality-checking, Sewil, Galaxy 9000, Halee
Soundtracking, Halee
Video editing, Sewil
Raw provider, Crunchyroll